http://www.albionagencies.com/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The privacy and security of the personal information pertaining to our customers is important to us. We collect, maintain, and disclose personal information about our customers in connection with the insurance policies our companies provide. Nonpublic personal information that we collect may include name, address, social security number, wage information, driving record, policy coverages, medical information or credit history. It may also include transaction information such as premium payment or claims history.
The information we collect is disclosed only to the insurance companies we work with and the consumer reporting agencies they use to obtain underwriting information.
Because we respect our customers’ privacy, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise disclose identity or other personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes.
We only disclose information about our applicants, customers, and former customers as permitted or required by law in conjunction with our normal insurance operations.
Search
Hours
Mon - Wed: 9:00am - 5:00pm
Thursday: 9:00am - 5:00pm
Friday: 9:00am - 5:00pm
Weekends - closed
CLOSED FRIDAY JULY 3
P: (585) 589-4477
F: (877) 257-9275
We will temporarily be keeping shortened hours on Thursdays until further notice. We will post when our hours return to normal and we begin staying open late on Thursday evenings again.
Thank you.
Calendar Contest
2020 Calendars
are HERE!
Sign Up for Our Quarterly Newsletter!
Email address:
First Name:
Last Name:
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Signing up will enter you to win a cup of coffee ON US!
Winners are drawn monthly and announced in our quarterly newsletter.
Click here to VIEW our most recent newsletters
Get a Quote
Open Maps Widget for Google Maps settings to configure the Google Maps API key. The map can't work without it. This is a Google's rule that all sites must follow.Related PostsAward Affirms ERIE’s Financial Strength By admin Wed, 27th Jul 11Headed to College?By Chris Wed, 11th Aug 10Are You Ready for Winter?By Chris Wed, 8th Dec 10Three steps to improving your insurance score: Part 1By Chris Wed, 4th Mar 09Update: Costs reduced for online defensive driver coursesBy Chris Mon, 18th Jan 10
InsuranceAuto InsuranceHomeowners InsuranceLife InsuranceGet a Free Quote
Customer ServiceReport an AccidentPay Your BillService Options
Our AgencyOur HistoryOur StaffContact Us
Learning CenterOur Blog
© 2014 Albion Agencies Insurance | Albion, NY. All rights reserved.
